Guide to the Ramón Hernández Tejano Music Collection
The Wittliff Collections
- Artist Files, 1922-2019, undated
  - Male Artist Files
    - La Tropa F - Clippings, 1993-2015, undated (Box 88, Folder 36)
    - La Tropa F - Audiovisual material, 1998, undated (Box 88, Folder 37)
    - Tropical Hawaii, undated (Box 88, Folder 38)
    - True Believers, 1985, undated (Box 88, Folder 39)
    - The True-King Band, 1986, 1990, undated (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Los Truenos de Texas - Photographs, undated (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Los Truenos de Texas - Album covers, 1988-1989, undated (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Los Truenos de Texas - Ramón Hernández material, 1988, undated (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Los Truenos de Texas - Clippings, 1988 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Los Truenos de Texas - Promotional materials, undated (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Felix Truvere & The Open Road, 2015, undated (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Turning Point, undated (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - The Twilites, undated (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Leroy U, undated (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - U.L., undated (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Los Unicos, 2001, undated (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Los Unicos - Audiovisual material, 2001, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Unison, 1998, undated (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Uptown Band, 1992-1998 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Urban Urbano, 2009-2018, undated (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Artie V. y Grupo Sauve, 2009, 2011, undated (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Roger V., 1988, 1992 (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Ruben V., 2003-2014 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Héctor Valadez, 2000, undated (Box 89, Folder 20)
    - Héctor Valadez - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 89, Folder 21)
    - Roberto Valderrama, 2010 (Box 89, Folder 22)
    - Albert Valdez, 1993 (Box 89, Folder 23)
    - Juan Cruz Valdez, undated (Box 89, Folder 24)
    - Valentino, 1987, undated (Box 89, Folder 25)
    - Valentino, undated (Box 89, Folder 26)
    - Ricky Valenz, 2013-2014, undated (Box 89, Folder 27)
    - Vallejo, undated (Box 89, Folder 28)
    - Ignacio Vallejo, undated (Box 89, Folder 29)
    - Valles Brothers Band, 2001, undated (Box 89, Folder 30)
    - Valor, 1999, undated (Box 89, Folder 31)
    - Angel Manuel Vargas, 1987, 2014, undated (Box 89, Folder 32)
    - Chris Varelas, 2017 (Box 89, Folder 33)
    - Edgar Vasquez y Sus Muchachos, 1996, undated (Box 89, Folder 34)
    - Mario Vasquez, 2011, undated (Box 89, Folder 35)
    - Moses Vasquez, 1968, undated (Box 89, Folder 36)
    - Roger Vasquez, undated (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Stevie Ray Vavages, undated (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Paul "Vee" & Southern Wind, 1995, undated (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Enrique Vela, 2007 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Óscar Vela, undated (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Ruben Vela - Photographs, undated (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Ruben Vela, undated (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Ruben Vela - Publicity, 1995-2007, undated (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Ruben Vela - Clippings, 1994-2011, undated (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Ruben Vela - Audiovisual material, 1999, undated (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Carlos Velasquez, undated (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Gilbert Velasquez, 2011, undated (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Roger Velasquez, 2006-2016, undated (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Roger Velasquez - Press kits, 2010 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Velocidad, 2014 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - La Venganza, undated (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - La Ventada, 2008 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Ventura, undated (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Dwayne Verheyden & The TexMeXplosion, 2010-2013, undated (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Verisimilitude, 2018 (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Los Veteranos, undated (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Veterans Band of Corpus Christi, undated (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Vida Alegre, undated (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Vidal, undated (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - Jaime Vidal, 2016, 2018, undated (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - Los Vidals, undated (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Juan Viesca - Photographs, 1943, undated (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Juan Viesca, undated (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - Juan Viesca - Correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - Juan Viesca - Concert and event publicity, 1979-1983, undated (Box 90, Folder 30)
    - Juan Viesca - Discography materials, 1981, undated (Box 90, Folder 31)
    - Juan Viesca - Clippings, 1958-1991, undated (Box 90, Folder 32)
    - Villa Band, undated (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Beto Villa - Photographs, undated (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Beto Villa, 1992-2008, undated (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Oscar Villa, 2008-2009 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Jaime Villalobos, 1992-1994 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Jaime Villalobos - Audiovisual material, [1994] (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Javier Villanueva, 2011 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Arturo Villarreal, 2012, undated (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Bruno Villarreal, 2008, undated (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Frutty Villarreal y Los Mavericks, 2009 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Jesse Villarreal, 2014 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Nick Villarreal - Photographs, undated (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Nick Villarreal - Personal, undated (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Nick Villarreal - Albums, undated (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Nick Villarreal - Publicity, 2000, undated (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Nick Villarreal - Ramón Hernández material, 1987, undated (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Nick Villarreal - Clippings, 1987-2017, undated (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Nick Villarreal - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Nick Villarreal, Sr., 1978 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Race Villarrreal, undated (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Ramiro Villarreal y Concepto Acústico, 2011 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Rey Villarreal, Sr., 2005 (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Ruco Villarreal, 2006, 2008, undated (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - Vission, undated (Box 91, Folder 24)
    - La Vista, undated (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - Ryan Vizcaino, undated (Box 91, Folder 26)
    - Ryan Vizcaino - Clippings, 2012-2016, undated (Box 91, Folder 27)
    - Ryan Vizcaino - Audiovisual materials, undated (Box 91, Folder 28)
    - Vizion, undated (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Voces Unidas, undated (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Volcán Conjunto Eruption, 2016-2017, undated (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Los Volcanes de Eddie Rodriguez, 2003 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Volcom, undated (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Von Army, 2009 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Mark Webber, 2010-2018 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Los Weebads del Norte, undated (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Kerry West, 1992, undated (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Kerry West - Audiovisual material, 1992 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - West Side Horns, 2014, 2016 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Los Wingos, undated (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Winterkat, 1986, undated (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - X, undated (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - X - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - X - Promotional material, undated (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - X-Tranos, 1991 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Xcezzo, undated (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Xelencia - Photographs, 1989, undated (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Xelencia - Album covers, 1992, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Xelencia - Ramón Hernández material, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - Xelencia - Clippings, 1988-1996, undated (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - Xicano Power, 2012 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - Xklusivo - Photographs, undated (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Xklusivo - Publicity, 1999, undated (Box 92, Folder 25)
    - Xklusivo - Ramón Hernández material, 1999, undated (Box 92, Folder 26)
    - Xklusivo - Clippings, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 27)
    - Xplosion, 2018, undated (Box 92, Folder 28)
    - Xplosion - Audiovisual material, 2018 (Box 92, Folder 29)
    - Xplosivo, 1995, undated (Box 92, Folder 30)
    - Xtremo, undated (Box 92, Folder 31)
    - Danny Yanez, Sr., 2011 (Box 92, Folder 32)
    - Joe Ybarra y Sangre Nueva - Photographs, undated (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Joe Ybarra y Sangre Nueva, 1990, undated (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Joe Ybarra y Sangre Nueva - Ramón Hernández material, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Joe Ybarra y Sangre Nueva - Clippings, 2014, undated (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Pedro Yerena, undated (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Yo La Tengo, undated (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Ron Young, undated (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - The Young Ones, 2016 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - The Yoyos, undated (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - A.J. Zamora, undated (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Albert Zamora - Photographs (1 of 4), 1994, 1999, undated (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Albert Zamora - Photographs (2 of 4), 1994, 1999, undated (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Albert Zamora - Photographs (3 of 4), 1994, 1999, undated (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Albert Zamora - Photographs (4 of 4), 1994, 1999, undated (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Albert Zamora - Publicity photographs, undated (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Albert Zamora - 35mm negatives (1 of 2), undated (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Albert Zamora - 35mm negatives (2 of 2), undated (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Albert Zamora - Concert and event photographs - Soaring Eagle Casino Concert, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Albert Zamora - Concert and event photographs - Tour - Memphis, [1999] (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Albert Zamora - Concert and event photographs - Tour - Mexico, [1999] (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Albert Zamora - Concert and event photographs - Tour - Ohio, [1999] (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Albert Zamora - Concert and event photographs - Miller Lite Event, [1999] (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Albert Zamora - Concert and event photographs - Grupo Centro De Discos Event, undated (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Albert Zamora - Concert and event photographs - Southwest Wholesale Event, undated (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Albert Zamora - Concert and event photographs - Tejano Music Awards, undated (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Albert Zamora, Albums1998, 2001, undated (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Albert Zamora - Publicity, 1999, undated (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Albert Zamora - Tour, 1999 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Albert Zamora - Ramón Hernández material, 1998, undated (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Albert Zamora - Clippings, 1994-2012, undated (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Albert Zamora - Audiovisual material, 1998, 2000 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Oscar Zamora, 1978, 1988, undated (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Roy Zamora, 1989, undated (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Santos Zamora y Su Conjunto, undated (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Zamorales, 2013, undated (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Rene Zapata y Grupo Presidente, 1995, undated (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Zarabande, 1995 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Los Zarate, 1988 (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - Gabriel Zavala, 2013, undated (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - Geno Zavala, undated (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - La Zekta, 1987, undated (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - Zeña, undated (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - Oscar Zepeda, 1990, undated (Box 94, Folder 25)
    - Fred Zimmerle y Su Conjunto Trio San Antonio, 1998, undated (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - Henry Zimmerle, 1984, 2000, undated (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - Henry Zimmerle - Ramón Hernández material, 1990, undated (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Henry Zimmerle - Clippings, 1989-2012, undated (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Jimmie Zimmerle, undated (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Joe Zimmerle, undated (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Zinzzero, undated (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Zinzzero - Audiovisual material, 2000 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Zoga Band, undated (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - The Zots, 2011 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Agapito Zuniga, 2009-2010, undated (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Art Zuniga, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Joe Zuniga, undated (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Sam Zuniga, undated (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Female Artist Files
    - 3 Latinas, 1998, undated (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Victoria Acosta, 2012-2014, undated (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Jeanine Acquart, 1995 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Aisha, undated (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Aixa (Inés A. Gómez), 1990 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Mary Alanis, 2018 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Natalie Alaniz, 1986, 1994 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Alex y Rio Grande, undated (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Alex y Rio Grande - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Alexxa, undated (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Flor Alicia, undated (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Alma, undated (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Alondra, 2001-2002, undated (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Alondra - Clippings, 2001-2002 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Alondra - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Ventura Alonso, 1995-2003, undated (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Alyson Alonzo, 2012-2018 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Monique Alvarado, 2000, undated (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Amanda, undated (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Amor y Pasion, 2000, undated (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Amor y Pasion - Audiovisual material, 2000 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Anani "La Charrita", undated (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Amber Anaya, undated (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - Angela, undated (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Angelica, 1992, undated (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - Annette y Axxion, 1996, undated (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - Teresa Araiza, undated (Box 96, Folder 27)
    - Phoebe Marie Arriaga, undated (Box 96, Folder 28)
    - Audi y Zentimiento, undated (Box 96, Folder 29)
    - Aurelia, undated (Box 96, Folder 30)
    - Ayala, undated (Box 96, Folder 31)
    - Azul, 2010, 2013 (Box 96, Folder 32)
    - Jessica Baeza, undated (Box 96, Folder 33)
    - Devin Banda, 2014, undated (Box 96, Folder 34)
    - Maria Teresa "Marité" Barcelata, 1985-1986, undated (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Maria Teresa "Marité" Barcelata - Clippings, 1986, undated (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Martha Barraza, undated (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Beatriz, 2003, undated (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Beatriz - Clippings, 2007-2018, undated (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Stephanie Bergara, 2016 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Eva Berrones, 1993 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Blanco y Grupo Cielo, 1995, undated (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Erika Bonilla, undated (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Ashley Borrero, undated (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Jennifer Bowen, 2017 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Suzy Bravo and the Soul Revue, 2012 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Briana, 2009, undated (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Briana - Audiovisual material, 2003, undated (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Brilliante, [1998]-1999, undated (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Byanka, undated (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Janie C. - Photographs, undated (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Janie C. - Personal, undated (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Janie C., 1999, undated (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - Janie C. -Ramón Hernández material, 1988, undated (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - Janie C. - Clippings, 2007, 2010, undated (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - Janie C. - Audiovisual material, 2000 (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - Crystal Caballero, undated (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - Chrystal Campbell, undated (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - Malena Cano, 1992, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - Laura Canales - Photographs (1 of 2), 1996, undated (Box 97, Folder 26)
    - Laura Canales - Photographs (2 of 2), 1996, undated (Box 97, Folder 27)
    - Laura Canales - Mounted photographs and clippings, undated (Box 97, Folder 28)
    - Laura Canales - Personal, 1986, 1997, undated (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Laura Canales - Albums, 1983-1994, undated (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Laura Canales - Publicity, 2005, 2009, undated (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Laura Canales - Ramón Hernández material, 1986-2005, undated (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Laura Canales - Clippings, 1983-2005, undated (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Laura Canales - Magazine issues, 1989, 1993 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Diane Cantu, undated (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Norma Cantu, undated (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Las Carazones Jovenes, undated (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Carmen y Laura, 2000, undated (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Christina Carrizales, undated (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Marietta Castillo, undated (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Monica Castro, 2009, 2013, undated (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Cecilia, 2000, undated (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Juliette Cedillo, 1996 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Martha Centeno, 1987, undated (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Vanessa Cerda-Alonzo, 2007-2010, undated (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Carmen Cervantes y Grupo, 2017 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - Lorissa Chapa, 2007, 2009 (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - Chavela y su Grupo Express, undated (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - Cathy Chavez - Photographs, undated (Box 98, Folder 21)
    - Cathy Chavez - Events, 1992, undated (Box 98, Folder 22)
    - Cathy Chavez - Publicity, 1987-1988, undated (Box 98, Folder 23)
    - Cathy Chavez - Ramón Hernández material, 1989, 1991, undated (Box 98, Folder 24)
    - Cathy Chavez - Clippings, 1988-1989, undated (Box 98, Folder 25)
    - Gina Chavez, 2014 (Box 98, Folder 26)
    - Italie Chavez, 2010 (Box 98, Folder 27)
    - Las Cherokee Chix, 1996 (Box 98, Folder 28)
    - Las Chicas Del Barrio, undated (Box 98, Folder 29)
    - Cindi & Klazz, [1989], undated (Box 98, Folder 30)
    - Cinnamon, 1989, undated (Box 98, Folder 31)
    - Carol Cisneros, undated (Box 98, Folder 32)
    - Sallie Cisneros, undated (Box 98, Folder 33)
    - City of San Antonio Folkloric Dancers, undated (Box 98, Folder 34)
    - Clarice, 2008 (Box 98, Folder 35)
    - Claudette, undated (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Claudia y La Logia, 2007 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Conjunto Clemencia, undated (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - La Conquista, 2003-2011 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Josey Contreras, 2013, undated (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Amanda Corral, undated (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Paula Cortes, 2015 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Janet Cortez (Perla Tapatia), 2008, 2014, undated (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Marisa Cortez, 2011, 2013, undated (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Verónica Cortez, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Corrine Cruz, 1989 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Yvette Cruz, undated (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - The Cruzers - Photographs, undated (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - The Cruzers - Albums, 1995 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - The Cruzers - Clipping, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Crystal N' Crew, undated (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Adeline Cuesta, 2006 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Celeste Curiel, 1999-2000, undated (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - Celeste Curiel - Clippings, 1999-2010 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Heather "Flor" De Anda, 1999 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - Star De Azlan, 2009 (Box 99, Folder 21)
    - Janis De Lara, undated (Box 99, Folder 22)
    - Claudia De Leon, undated (Box 99, Folder 23)
    - Judi De Leon, 1995-2018, undated (Box 99, Folder 24)
    - Judi De Leon - Audiovisual material, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 25)
    - Sonia Marie DeLeón, undated (Box 99, Folder 26)
    - Angela De Los Santos, undated (Box 99, Folder 27)
    - Mari Del Castillo, 1978, undated (Box 99, Folder 28)
    - Vanessa Del Fierro, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 29)
    - Ana Maria Del Rio, undated (Box 99, Folder 30)
    - Dahlia, 1996 (Box 99, Folder 31)
    - DaShenna y Caliente, 2003 (Box 99, Folder 32)
    - Paola Davalos, 2012-2013, undated (Box 99, Folder 33)
    - Paola Davalos - Clippings, 2012, undated (Box 99, Folder 34)
    - Paula DeAnda, 2007 (Box 99, Folder 35)
    - Delia y Culturas, undated (Box 99, Folder 36)
    - Deya, 2002, undated (Box 99, Folder 37)
    - Deya - Clippings, 2001-2003, undated (Box 99, Folder 38)
    - Diane & Ernesto, undated (Box 99, Folder 39)
    - Dinora, undated (Box 99, Folder 40)
    - Dolores, undated (Box 99, Folder 41)
    - Azeneth Dominguez, 2012 (Box 99, Folder 42)
    - Shirley Dominguez, undated (Box 99, Folder 43)
    - Sylvia Donley, undated (Box 99, Folder 44)
    - Dori Ann y Grupo Evolucion, 2003 (Box 99, Folder 45)
    - Dorian, undated (Box 99, Folder 46)
    - The Dreamliners, 2016, undated (Box 99, Folder 47)
    - Norma Duran, 2013 (Box 99, Folder 48)
    - Maria Elena, 2001, undated (Box 99, Folder 49)
    - Norma Eliza - Photographs, 1987, undated (Box 99, Folder 50)
    - Norma Eliza - Publicity, undated (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Norma Eliza - Albums, undated (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Norma Eliza - Ramón Hernández material, 1988, 1994, undated (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Norma Eliza - Clippings, 1988-1995, undated (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Norma Eliza - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Elizabeth, undated (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Elizabeth - Clippings, 2008-2010, undated (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Elizabeth - Audiovisual material, 2009 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Eloisa y Su Grupo Suave, undated (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Elora and Gasoline Alley, 2014 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Guadalupe Enriquez, 2001 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Linda Escobar - Photographs, 1966-1977, undated (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Linda Escobar - Publicity photographs, undated (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Linda Escobar - Personal, undated (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Linda Escobar - Concert and events, 2004, 2014, undated (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Linda Escobar - Albums, 1989, 1993, undated (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Linda Escobar - Publicity, 2002, undated (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Linda Escobar - Ramón Hernández material, 1989-2004, undated (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Linda Escobar - Clippings, 2000-2015, undated (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - Linda Escobar - Audiovisual material, 1982-2002, undated (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - Linda Escobar - Promotional material, 2014, undated (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - Veronica Escobar, undated (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - L. Beatriz Escudero, 1990 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Esmeralda - Photographs, 1981, undated (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Esmeralda - Album covers, 1977, 1992 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Esmeralda - Publicity, [1993], undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Esmeralda - Ramón Hernández material, 1991, undated (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Esmeralda - Clippings, 1978-1993, undated (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Espada y Diamante, undated (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Janie Esparza, 1994, undated (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Angel Espinoza, [1997] (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Connie Espinoza, 2000 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Jennifer Espinoza, 2011 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Paula Estrada - Photographs, 1995, undated (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Paula Estrada - Personal, 1960-1961, undated (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Paula Estrada - Ramón Hernández material, 1995-2007, undated (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Paula Estrada - Clippings, 1997, 2010, undated (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Paula Estrada - Audiovisual material, 2007 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Valentina Estrada, 2011-2012, undated (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Fabianna, undated (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Femina-X, 2017-2018 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Las Fenix, 2011, 2015, undated (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Photographs, undated (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Mounted photographs and exhibition labels (1 of 2), undated (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Mounted photographs and exhibition labels (2 of 2), undated (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Personal-, undated (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Concert and event publicity, 1985-2000, undated (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Albums, 1987, undated (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Business correspondence, 1998 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Rosita Fernandez, undated (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Ramón Hernández material, 1983-2007, undated (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Clippings, 1983-1999 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Clippings, 2002-2014 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Rosita Fernandez - Clippings, undated (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Rosita Fernandez - "Rosita" Vanity License Plates (1 of 2), 1967-1993, undated (Box 103)
    - Rosita Fernandez - "Rosita" Vanity License Plates (2 of 2), 1967-1993, undated (Box 104)
    - Valerie Fernandez, 2008 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Fifth Harmony, 2012-2013 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Las Florecitas, 2000, 2005, undated (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Veronica Flores, 2016, undated (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Annette Fradera, 1989 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Lisa Frank, 2010 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Chelsea G., 2014, undated (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Sandy G. y Los Gavilanes, undated (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Teri G., undated (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Yolanda Gaitan, undated (Box 105, Folder 10)